Deal with her.
Molly's Game is a drama, crime film directed by Aaron Sorkin.
Molly Bloom, a young skier and former Olympic hopeful becomes a successful entrepreneur (and a target
of an FBI investigation) when she establishes a high-stakes, international poker game.
Molly Bloom, played by Jessica Chastain.
Charlie Jaffey, played by Idris Elba.
Larry Bloom, played by Kevin Costner.
Player X, played by Michael Cera.
Dean Keith, played by Jeremy Strong.
Douglas Downey, played by Chris O'Dowd.
Molly's Game is a 2017 American biographical film written and directed by Aaron Sorkin (in his directorial debut), based on the 2014 memoir by Molly Bloom, who makes reference to Alimzhan Tokhtakhunov's association with running an illegal gambling ring and "a
sophisticated Russian organized crime money-laundering network that operated out of unit 63A in Trump Tower in New York." It stars Jessica Chastain, Idris Elba, Kevin Costner, Michael Cera, Jeremy Strong, Chris O'Dowd, Joe Keery, Brian D'Arcy James, and Bill Camp.
The film follows Bloom (Chastain), who becomes the target of an FBI investigation after the underground poker
empire she runs for Hollywood celebrities, athletes, business tycoons, and the Russian mob is exposed.
Principal photography began in November 2016 in Toronto, Ontario, Canada.
The film premiered on September 8, 2017, at the Toronto International Film Festival, and began a limited theatrical release in the United States on
December 25, 2017, by STX Entertainment, then going to world-wide distribution January 5, 2018, and grossed $59 million worldwide.
Molly's Game received positive reviews, with particular praise for Sorkin's screenplay, as well as Chastain and
Elba's performances, with that of the former considered one of the best of her career by some critics.
The film earned Chastain a Golden Globe nomination for Best Actress – Drama, while Sorkin earned nominations for his
screenplay at the Academy Awards, Golden Globes, Writers Guild of America Awards, and BAFTA Awards.
The film explores themes of new york city, court,
poker, gambling, bratva (russian mafia).
The tone is uplifting and emotional.